BU Records: Chancellor's Office (Abner Vernon McCall), Inclusive: 1980-1988, undated, Bulk: 1981-1985
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- People, 1981-1988, undated; 3
  - S — Correspondence (2 of 2), 1981-1984 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - T — Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - V — Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - W — Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Watson, Allan, 1983-1985 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Weatherby, Hon. Jim W., 1983-1985 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Personal, 1982-1985, undated; 4
  This series includes McCall's appointment books and speeches from his time as Chancellor. McCall's 1981 appointment book is in BU Records: Office of the President (Abner Vernon McCall). This series is in average condition.
  - Appointment Book, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Appointment Book, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Appointment Book, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Appointment Book, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Eulogies, 1984, undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Speeches — Law, 1982-1983, undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Speeches — Love — Park Cities Baptist Church, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Speeches — Patriotism, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Speeches — Tributes, 1983-1985 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Speeches — Welcome Week, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 7)